<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Shiqi Ye (叶仕奇)</title>
    <link>https://KuntingUSTC.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Shiqi Ye (叶仕奇)</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://KuntingUSTC.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://KuntingUSTC.github.io/docs/about-me/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://KuntingUSTC.github.io/docs/about-me/</guid>
      <description>Hi, my name is Shiqi Ye. I&amp;rsquo;m a third-year Joint Ph.D. student between the Chow Institute, Xiamen University and the Academy of Mathematics and Systems Science, Chinese Academy of Sciences. I am grateful to be advised by Prof. Tingguo Zheng, Prof. Yongmiao Hong, and Prof. Ming Lin.
My research areas include econometrics, financial econometrics, climate economics, regional economics, energy economics, and the Chinese economy.
My current research is mainly focused on:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://KuntingUSTC.github.io/docs/experience/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://KuntingUSTC.github.io/docs/experience/</guid>
      <description>Education P.h.D. Econometrices, Chow Institue, 2024 (expected). M.A. Applied Economics and Econometrices, University of Southern California, 2020. B.A. Mathematics and Applied Mathematics, University of Science and Technology of China, 2018. Experiences Academy of Mathematics and Systems Science at Chinese Academy of Sciences
Joint Ph.D. student, 2022.09-2023.09. Fundamental Scientific Center for Economic Modeling and Economic Policy Studies
research assistent, 2022.03-now. Projects “Dual Carbon” Goal, Transition Risk, and Industry Connectedness — Analysis Based on High-Dimensional Time-Frequency Complex Network</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://KuntingUSTC.github.io/docs/research/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://KuntingUSTC.github.io/docs/research/</guid>
      <description>Published Papers “Attention-aware Multi-hop Trust Inference in Online Social Networks”
(with Rongwei Xu, Guanfeng Liu, Xianmei Hua, Xuyun Zhang, and Junwen Lu).
&amp;mdash;International Conference on Data Science and Advanced Analytics, (2022) | Paper | Slide | Working Papers “Fast Estimation of a Large TVP-VAR Model with Score-Driven Volatilities”
(with Tingguo Zheng and Yongmiao Hong). | Paper🔒 | Slide | “Cholesky GAS Models for Large Time-Varying Covariance Matrices”
(with Tingguo Zheng). | Paper🔒 | Slide | “Score-Driven Time-Varying Parameter VAR Models”</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://KuntingUSTC.github.io/docs/links/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://KuntingUSTC.github.io/docs/links/</guid>
      <description>Symposium on High Dimensional Complex Systems (Holders: Shiqi Ye and Hongyin Zhang) October 12, 2020, first meeting:
&amp;ldquo;Bayesian Dynamic Tensor Regression&amp;rdquo; (Speaker: Shiqi Ye) | Paper | Slide | Video🔒 | October 26, 2022, second meeting:
&amp;ldquo;A Comparison of the Influence of Sino-US Economic Factors on Bilateral Exchange Rates&amp;rdquo; (Speaker: Linyan Chen) | Paper🔒 | &amp;ldquo;Estimation and Inference of Impulse Response by Local Projection&amp;rdquo; (Speaker: Hongyin Zhang) | Papers | Slide | Video🔒 | November 9, 2022, third meeting:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://KuntingUSTC.github.io/docs/miscellaneous/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://KuntingUSTC.github.io/docs/miscellaneous/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://KuntingUSTC.github.io/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Jan 2022 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://KuntingUSTC.github.io/about/</guid>
      <description>Our website builds with Hugo static site generator and Mainroad theme. This demo allows you to see what Mainroad based website looks like before deciding to go with it. Just keep in mind that the current demo shows the basics, a small part of what the combination of Hugo and Mainroad can do.
About Mainroad Mainroad is a responsive, simple, clean and content-focused Hugo theme based on the MH Magazine lite WordPress theme.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://KuntingUSTC.github.io/home/about-me/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://KuntingUSTC.github.io/home/about-me/</guid>
      <description>Shiqi Ye is a third-year Joint Ph.D. student between the Chow Institute, Xiamen University and the Academy of Mathematics and Systems Science, Chinese Academy of Sciences.
His research areas include econometrics, financial econometrics, climate economics, regional economics, energy economics, and the Chinese economy.
His current research is mainly focused on:
Estimate high-dimensional time-varying coefficients vector-autoregressive models; Extend the matrix-valued autoregressive model to allow for multiple matrices; Investigate the impacts of climate risk on the expected growth and growth-at-risk in China; Construct the urban financial condition index, and examine its impact on the growth of housing prices; Combine a large DCC-GARCH model with MIDAS and construct a high-dimensional short- and long-term time-varying correlation network of financial markets.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
