<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Documentation on Shiqi Ye (叶仕奇)</title>
    <link>https://KuntingUSTC.github.io/docs/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Documentation on Shiqi Ye (叶仕奇)</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://KuntingUSTC.github.io/docs/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://KuntingUSTC.github.io/docs/about-me/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://KuntingUSTC.github.io/docs/about-me/</guid>
      <description>Hi, my name is Shiqi Ye. I&amp;rsquo;m a third-year joint Ph.D. student at the Chow Institute at Xiamen University and the Academy of Mathematics and Systems Science at Chinese Academy of Sciences. I am grateful to be advised by Prof. Tingguo Zheng, Prof. Yongmiao Hong, and Prof. Ming Lin.
My research areas include econometrics, financial econometrics, climate economics, regional economics, energy economics, and the Chinese economy.
My current research is mainly focus on:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://KuntingUSTC.github.io/docs/experience/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://KuntingUSTC.github.io/docs/experience/</guid>
      <description>Education P.h.D. Econometrices, Chow Institue, 2024 (expected). M.A. Econometrices and Applied Econometrices, University of Southern California, 2020. B.A. Mathematics and Applied Mathematics, University of Science and Technology of China, 2018. </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://KuntingUSTC.github.io/docs/research/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://KuntingUSTC.github.io/docs/research/</guid>
      <description>Published Papers “Attention-aware Multi-hop Trust Inference in Online Social Networks”
(with Rongwei Xu, Guanfeng Liu, Xianmei Hua, Xuyun Zhang, and Junwen Lu).
&amp;mdash;International Conference on Data Science and Advanced Analytics, (2022) Working Papers “Fast Estimation of a Large TVP-VAR Model with Score-Driven Volatilities”
(with Tingguo Zheng and Yongmiao Hong). “Cholesky GAS Models for Large Time-varying Covariance Matrices”
(with Tingguo Zheng). “Score-Driven Time-Varying Parameter VAR Models”
(with Tingguo Zheng). “House Price Connectedness and Information Transmission”</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
