<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Documentation on Shiqi Ye (叶仕奇)</title>
    <link>https://KuntingUSTC.github.io/docs/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Documentation on Shiqi Ye (叶仕奇)</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://KuntingUSTC.github.io/docs/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://KuntingUSTC.github.io/docs/about-me/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://KuntingUSTC.github.io/docs/about-me/</guid>
      <description>Hi, my name is Shiqi Ye. I&amp;rsquo;m a third-year Joint Ph.D. student between the Chow Institute, Xiamen University and the Academy of Mathematics and Systems Science, Chinese Academy of Sciences. I am grateful to be advised by Prof. Tingguo Zheng, Prof. Yongmiao Hong, and Prof. Ming Lin.
My research areas include econometrics, financial econometrics, climate economics, regional economics, energy economics, and the Chinese economy.
My current research is mainly focused on:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://KuntingUSTC.github.io/docs/experience/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://KuntingUSTC.github.io/docs/experience/</guid>
      <description>Education P.h.D. Econometrices, Chow Institue, 2024 (expected). M.A. Applied Economics and Econometrices, University of Southern California, 2020. B.A. Mathematics and Applied Mathematics, University of Science and Technology of China, 2018. Experiences Academy of Mathematics and Systems Science at Chinese Academy of Sciences
joint Ph.D. student, 2022.09-2023.09. Fundamental Scientific Center for Economic Modeling and Economic Policy Studies
research assistent, 2022.03-now. Projects “Dual Carbon” Goal, Transition Risk, and Industry Connectedness — Analysis Based on High-Dimensional Time-Frequency Complex Network</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://KuntingUSTC.github.io/docs/links/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://KuntingUSTC.github.io/docs/links/</guid>
      <description>Symposium on High Dimensional Complex Systems (Holders: Shiqi Ye and Hongyin Zhang) October 12, 2020, first meeting:
&amp;ldquo;Bayesian Dynamic Tensor Regression&amp;rdquo; (Speaker: Shiqi Ye) | Paper | Slide | Vedio🔒 | October 26, 2022, second meeting:
&amp;ldquo;A Comparison of the Influence of Sino-US Economic Factors on Bilateral Exchange Rates&amp;rdquo; (Speaker: Linyan Chen) | Paper🔒 | &amp;ldquo;Estimation and Inference of Impulse Response by Local Projection&amp;rdquo; (Speaker: Hongyin Zhang) | Papers | Slide | Vedio🔒 | November 9, 2022, third meeting:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://KuntingUSTC.github.io/docs/research/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://KuntingUSTC.github.io/docs/research/</guid>
      <description>Published Papers “Attention-aware Multi-hop Trust Inference in Online Social Networks”
(with Rongwei Xu, Guanfeng Liu, Xianmei Hua, Xuyun Zhang, and Junwen Lu).
&amp;mdash;International Conference on Data Science and Advanced Analytics, (2022) | Paper | Slide | Working Papers “Fast Estimation of a Large TVP-VAR Model with Score-Driven Volatilities”
(with Tingguo Zheng and Yongmiao Hong). | Paper🔒 | Slide | “Cholesky GAS Models for Large Time-Varying Covariance Matrices”
(with Tingguo Zheng). | Paper🔒 | Slide | “Score-Driven Time-Varying Parameter VAR Models”</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
